notdoppler.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy

Last updated June 27, 2018

Not Doppler Pty Limited (ABN: 28 158 472 363)("Not Doppler") is committed to ensuring our website (www.notdoppler.com) is a fun and safe environment. Not Doppler does not actively run a user registration system, forum, chat or instant messaging function and thereby does not directly collect any personally identifiable information about our users except for persistent identifiers (cookies) used in our advertising and analytics operations as noted below. Some games featured or hosted on Not Doppler that are managed by third-party publishers may contain features such as user registration systems, forums, chat rooms and so forth; which are not managed by Not Doppler and are dictated by the privacy policy of the game's publisher.

Not Doppler does however collect some basic browsing related data for advertising and analytics purposes. Please consult the below privacy policy which contains further details:

**Cookies and data collected:**  
Not Doppler collects information about the way visitors and players are using our website through the use of Google Analytics and its related cookie(s). The goal of collecting this data is to make better informed decisions about what games our users are more likely to enjoy and to help improve the experience on Not Doppler. The type of information that Google Analytics collects includes browser and operating system type, country, pages visited, time spent on site, date/time stamp and broad demographic information. Google Analytics does not collect any sensitive information, and personally identifiable information is limited only to the cookie stored for tracking purposes. This data collected remains anonymous and is aggregated for any analysis.

Certain games on Not Doppler will create "Local shared objects" which allow the game to save game progress so that when you return you can pick up from where you left off. These save files are usually stored on your own computer and not shared with any third parties. However for games that are multi-player or include the use of a server with a user account system, this data may instead be stored in a cloud-based service. In this instance, storage and retrieval of such data is dictated by the privacy policy of such game publisher offering the service.

Please see Advertising section below for further details on cookies.

**Advertising:**  
Not Doppler is a free to use website and generates revenue through third-party advertising on the website. Without the support of this advertising Not Doppler would not be able to provide new games every Thursday. These third-party advertising companies may collect and use information about your visits to this and other websites to help determine which advertisements are most suited to your interests and measure performance of any advertising campaigns. In order to collect this information, the third-party may use a cookie or other such methods including javascript codes. Not Doppler has no influence over the policies of third-party advertising networks (except our ability to discontinue using their services).

The information they collect may be considered personally identifiable, or it could be considered personally identifiable in certain circumstances. This information is only ever used for our legitimate business interests and will never be sold or shared by us.

Nevertheless, the data is provided to us by third parties. While we use all reasonable commercial endeavours to ensure that they adhere to any applicable laws, we encourage you to familiarise yourself with their data policies.

If you would like more information about advertising practices and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit Google's Advertising and Privacy page:  
http://www.google.com.au/policies/technologies/ads/

**Opt Out of targeted advertising on Notdoppler.com:**  
Targeted advertising using browser behaviour is designed to ensure users see more relevant advertising based on their interests. If you prefer not to see targeted advertising from our advertising partners you can opt out of these services, or find out more information about their privacy policies by following the below links: _Freestar.io_  
[Privacy Policy & Opt Out](https://freestar.io/data-policy) _Google Analytics & Google AdSense_  
[Opt Out](https://adssettings.google.com/) _CPMStar:_  
[Opt Out](http://server.cpmstar.com/optout.aspx) **External Links:**  
Not Doppler may link to other web sites and is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of these external sites. Some games on Not Doppler also contain links to external sites or may contain requests for personal information for gameplay purposes (e.g. account registration or chatroom features) which are governed by their own individual privacy policies. All users should therefore also be aware of the individual privacy policies within any game that requests personal information such as name or email address. **Age Limit:**  
Not Doppler is designed for persons aged 13 over, and those under 13 should not browse the website without direct parental supervision. While Not Doppler does not offer any forums, chat rooms, user registration systems or similar mechanisms where information can be shared, if you have concern that information related to the privacy of children has been submitted to Not Doppler, please contact us at [privacy@notdoppler.com](mailto:privacy@notdoppler.com) **Help and Support:**  
Not Doppler provides a support email address ([contact@notdoppler.com](mailto:contact@notdoppler.com)) where users may share comments, thoughts, business opportunities or request support with any technical difficulties. From time to time, Not Doppler also allows users to provide feedback or answer survey questions to help improve the quality of the website.  
If you contact us with a comment or query, Not Doppler will keep a copy of any personal information you provide. This is so that we can respond to your comments and questions as a part of our commitment to providing you with player support. If you contact us directly for any reason, we also keep a copy of that correspondence. **Not Doppler on your Mobile:**  
Not Doppler also publishes and sells mobile games for the iOS and Android mobile platforms. These games may be premium (charge an upfront fee) or free-to-play, with in-game advertising and/or in-game transactions. Please refer to the individual privacy policy of each game below for more information on what data is collected and used:  
[Earn to Die](http://notdoppler.com/earntodie/privacypolicy.php) **Updates to this Privacy Policy:**  
This Privacy Policy may be changed or modified from time to time. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to this page to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back to our Privacy Policy periodically. **Access to your data, and permanent deletion of your data**  
Not Doppler will retain your data only as necessary for our legitimate business interests, such as to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

No matter how we come in contact with your data, you have the right to access the data Not Doppler holds about you and to update and/or correct it, subject to certain exceptions.

**Data Subject Requests**  
In the event that you send a data subject request to Not Doppler, or one of our third-party partners informs us that you have contacted them directly about your personal data they collected while you were using our service, We will respond to that request in accordance with any applicable legislation.

If you wish to know what data we hold about you, if any, please make out your request to us in writing at the email address listed below. Please be aware that in order to protect the information in Our control, We will require identification from you before releasing any information.

**Disclosure, and Security of Your Information**  
We will not sell, trade, rent or disclose any of the personal information you provide to us for any reason, without your prior consent. Otherwise, your Personal Information will only be disclosed where required or allowable by law.

Your Personal Information is stored offsite in a manner that reasonably protects it from misuse, loss, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.

**General & Contact us:**  
By using this site, you accept the Not Doppler Online Privacy Policy. If you have any concerns please contact us at [privacy@notdoppler.com](mailto:privacy@notdoppler.com). We hope you continue to enjoy your experience on Not Doppler.
